    [
            {"question": "ska", "answer": "shall"},
            {"question": "har", "answer": "has"},
            {"question": "kan", "answer": "can"},
            {"question": "m책ste", "answer": "must"},
            {"question": "skall", "answer": "shall"},
            {"question": "har", "answer": "has"},
            {"question": "채r", "answer": "is"},
            {"question": "var", "answer": "was"},
            {"question": "blir", "answer": "becomes"},
            {"question": "blev", "answer": "became"},
            {"question": "kommer", "answer": "comes"},
            {"question": "kom", "answer": "came"},
            {"question": "g책r", "answer": "goes"},
            {"question": "gick", "answer": "went"},
            {"question": "f책r", "answer": "gets"},
            {"question": "fick", "answer": "got"},
            {"question": "vill", "answer": "wants"},
            {"question": "ville", "answer": "wanted"}
    ]
    
